Guide to the Rice Center for Community Design + Research records, 1968-1987 UA 181
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Community design and research files, 1968-1987, 214438
  - Preleminary Audit of Business Impacting Attributes of the Houston Region. Prepared for the Houston Economic Development Council. Rice Center; September 1984, 214844 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Preliminary Identification of Industrial Sectors to Target for Houston Business Development. Prepared for the Houston Economic Development Council. Rice Center; October 1984, 214845 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Analysis of Alternative Industrial Development Scenarios for Houston. Prepared for the Houston Venture Capital Association. Rice Center; November 1984, 214846 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Rivercrest Subdivision Deed Restrictions Analysis. Prepared for Ivor B. Clark, Inc. Rice Center; November 1984, 214847 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Follow-Up Analysis of Industrial Sectors to Target for Houston Business Development. Prepared for the Houston Economic Development Council. Rice Center; November 1984, 214848 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Health-Related Industries: Preliminary Targets for Houston. Prepared for the Houston Economic Development Council. Rice Center; December 1984, 214849 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Rice Center Research Briefs on Houston; April 1979 - October 1985, 214850 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Rice Center Research Briefs on Dallas; January 1984, September 1984, and August 1985, 214851 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rice Center Briefs on San Antonio; August 1984, January 1985, May 1985, and June 1985, 214852 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Rice Center Research Summaries; September 1976 - December 1988, 214853 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Rice Center Research Profiles; May 1984 and January 1985, 214854 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Rice Center Area Profiles, 1, A Growth in San Antonio; May 1986, and 2, A Growth Market in Houston; May 1986, 214855 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Rice Center Houston Profiles; January 1987 - January 1989, 214856 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Rice Center Houston Market Brief; 2 September 1980 - April 1987, 214857 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - The Joint Center for Urban Mobility Research, Joint Center Exchange; October 1984, 214858 (Box 9, Folder 28)